

WORK EXPERIENCE

Gokuraku - Spanish Cybercafe

1999 - 2007

Computer technician in a Cybercafe.

Spanish Navy

2007 - 2017

Administration and Electromechanical Engineering/

EDUCATION

RAUL PAYA

Game Developer

PROFILE

A 39 years old Navy retiree with great enthusiasm about games across all platforms and game innovation, I have been studying programming by myself from scratch as a hobby since my young age.

My biggest influence is Super Nintendo and Japanese RPG.

So I came to Japan in 2017 to pursue official study of programming and look for a job as a developer.

I want to share my insights and make unique games and apps, with my identity defined by navy values.

In my personal portfolio I post my work that I enjoy doing during spare time and that I have learnt.

CONTACT

PHONE: 070-4471-0132

WEBSITE: https://raulet.dev/

EMAIL: contact@raulet.dev

EE. Antonio de Escaño

2011-2013

Electromechanical Engineering in a Vocational School.

Intercultural Japanese Language School

2017-2019

Japanes language.

Yamanashi Information Systems

2019-2021

Software Developing in a Vocational School

Certificates

- C/C++
- Java.
- Jw-CAD.
- JLPT N3.

SKILLS

Spanish	English	Japanese
C / C++ / C#	Unity	Java
Lua	HTML	CSS
Visual Basic	PHP	MySQL
Access	Excel	Jw-CAD